Guide to the Henry Geldzahler Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- December 1999 Acquisition, circa 1945-1996; 1; 39.04; (43 boxes)
  - Isamu Noguchi: approximately 70 page file including xerox typed drafts of preface by Geldzahler with corrections in his hand; typed xerox quotes by I.S.; xerox typed letter from Ronald Reagan regarding the opening of I.N. Garden Museum; inventory list of sculpture museum (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Kenneth Noland: approximately 50 page file including 8 page single spaced typescript with extensive editing in Geldzahler's hand (pencil and ink),drafts of essay by Geldzahler; 5 pages legal paper handwritten, ink and pencil, notes by Geldzahler; artists inventory and chronology; invitations; catalogue-Andre Emmerich Gallery 1980; clippings (xerox copies), 1980, undated (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Korea Show: 13 page file including invoices and handwritten list of artists names, for unrealized exhibit of American Art in Korea, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - David Park: 14 page file and catalogues - 5 pages handwritten notes on legal paper by Geldzahler; 8 page typed xerox hand-corrected essay by Geldzahler; 1 slide with typed note in envelope from Ed Brinkely; catalogue-Maxwell Gallery 1970 and Salander-O'Reilly Galleries 1983 (?) with hand ink notes by Geldzahler (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Parrish Art Museum: 2 page file - business letters to Geldzahler (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Domenico Paulon: approximately 85 page file - Mostly xerox artist sketches and xerox photos; typed original and xerox hand corrected essay drafts by Geldzahler (12 pages each), one with hand corrected by D.P. (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Pop Art Catalogue: approximately 40 page file - all various correspondence regarding contracts and distribution of "Pop Art 1955-1970" (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Proposals For Shows: 5 page unsent original typed hand signed letter to Janet Salinger by Geldzahler of ideas for art shows with list of suggested artist (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Public Places/Private Art: 2 copies of a 30 page loose bound proposal for television documentary of Public Art in America prepared by Walter Arensberg, seeking his participation (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - I.M. Pei: 36 page typed interview (Geldzahler and IMP) regarding Pei's renovation of the Louvre; a sixteen page edited draft of same, by Geldzahler (pen) and RF (pencil); contract with Elle Publishing; drawing and 2 slides of Maquette Grandeur displayed in Louvre with letter from Pei's secretary (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Pollock-Krasner Foundation: 16 page printed booklet - annual report 1985-1986; 1 page 1987 financial update; typed 1 page form letter regarding 1985-1986 report, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - P.S.1.: approximately 90 page file, from Geldzahler's tenure as Distinguished Guest Curator (Box 8, Folder 307)
    1) 25 page typed 2nd draft - September 20, 1989 for Underknown exhibition including artist bios; 2) xeroxes of press releases; 3) grant applications; 4) newspaper clippings; 5) PS1 newsletter 1984; 6) numerous correspondence to Geldzahler, handwritten and typed - mostly thank you notes for various exhibitions; 7) typed, hand corrected draft of an exhibition proposal (never realized) titled "Artist's Crafts" including Ken Price, Wendell Castle, Dale Chihuly.
  - Wally Putnam: Material sent to Geldzahler by W.P. including slides, resume, catalogues and typed introductory correspondence - all within a black 8x10 envelope; 2 typed hand signed letters to Geldzahler from WP; 26 page typed xerox manuscript by WP - "Rothko Seen Again" - 2 copies, 1987-1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Press Clippings: Vanity Fair, July 1986, page 86. Time, July 14, 1986, page 48 and numerous newspaper clippings regarding Venice Binnale - all in 8x10 manila envelope; numerous clippings, original and xerox regarding Geldzahler from 1982-1988 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Rauschenberg: 2 8x10 photos of collages and 1 transparency; 1 envelope with 5 slides (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - Releases: 4 page file - typed correspondence to Geldzahler asking permission to use his writing (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Representations of America: approximately 60 page file, mostly typescript with emendations in ink by Geldzahler. An exhibition Geldzahler organized in 1977 at the Pushkin Museum, here begun to be reworked and expanded into a book. Some typed letters and memos by Geldzahler to that end. (Project unrealized) (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Rockefeller Brochure Material and Ray King: Brochure and original and xerox manuscript regarding art in Rockefeller Center (approximately 30 pages); approximately 40 pages mostly xerox clippings regarding artist Ray King - including 1 page slides and 1 8x10 photo of Ray at work. (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Rockefeller Center (Box 8, Folder 314)
    1) 53 page xerox insurance summary and index of contents in Radio City Music Hall; 2) Invoices by Geldzahler to Rockefeller Group for consultation services; 3) Rainbow Art Program brochures; 4) Typed correspondence regarding artwork for Rainbow Room; 5) 10 page typescript describing the art and artists included in the newly renovated Rainbow Room at Rockefeller Center, including Chihuly, Dan Dailey, Moulthrop, Wm Morris, Nancy Graves etc.
  - Rosenquist: approximately 35 page file regarding article by Geldzahler for Architectural Digest including correspondence - contracts with A.D.; 10 page legal paper, typed and handwritten draft by Geldzahler and notes; various typed and pasted, hand corrected drafts "James Rosenquist's New Studio;" 7 5x7 color photos of J.R. studio; 1 8x10 B&W photo of painting (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Clifford Ross: 25 page xeroxes manuscript by C.R. "The Annals of Abstract Expressionism"; 1 page typed hand signed letter by Geldzahler to Yale University Press regarding manuscript; 1 page typed hand signed letter by CR to Geldzahler regarding manuscript (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Ruder Finn and Rotman: 1 page letter typed - hand signed by David Finn to Geldzahler regarding possibility of working together (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Italo Scanga: 1 page typed letter, hand signed, by I.S. to Geldzahler with enclosed transparency (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - Scull - Portrait of Ethel 38 page file: all legal correspondence and depositions regarding a portrait of Ethel Scull by Warhol - was it or was it not given to Met Museum lawsuit (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Julian Schnabel Statement (Agony has many faces...) Approximately 30 page file, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 320)
    1) 2 xerox copies of a 5 page hand corr. typed draft "Julian Schnabel - Some Thoughts", June 28th, 1983 by Geldzahler; 3 page typed original draft, hand corrected, ink; 2) 2 xerox copies of 5 page typed "Statement by J.S."; 3 page typed xerox draft of J.S. statement with corrections by Geldzahler; 3) Grey envelope with transparency and handwritten notes, ink, by J.S. verifying purchase of painting by Geldzahler for $500 in 1976 and one handwritten note, ink, from Bruno B.....(?) verifying his purchase of same painting from Geldzahler for 25,000 in 1983, signed by Geldzahler
  - Raymond Foye Letters from Madras (India): 14 handwritten, ink, letters to Geldzahler from Raymond Foye; 1 handwritten postcard, ink; 1 cable dispatch - regarding life with Clementes, travel etc. (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Richard Serra: approximately 90 page file - letters, testimonies, xerox clippings, etc. all regarding the sculpture "Tilted Are" by R.S. placed in Federal Courthouse and the city's move to destroy it. Two typescript letter signed by RS to Geldzahler (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Pam Smilow: 2 page typed resume and gallery invitations (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Joel Sokolov: 3 page file - 1 typed draft of recommendation letter, unsigned original; 1 page xerox typed recommendation letter "Dear Sir or Madam" signed by Geldzahler, ink,; 1 8x10 B&W photo of Geldzahler by J.S. undated (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Squat Theatre: 25 page file - all seems to be by Harry Newton - xerox typed, hand corrected, ink, "Brain storming" regarding theatre projects and miscellaneous ideas; 1 collage made from magazine contents with handwriting regarding birth of son (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Larry Stanton: approximately 15 page file. 4 page xerox typed 4/86 "A Tribute to Larry" by Julia A. Mayo; 13 page "Larry Stanton" by Arthur Lambert, typed xerox; 2 page xerox clipping from The Advocate; 1 page typed hand signed letter by ? regarding Mayo manuscript (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - Jean Stein Interview: two copies, 60 pages each, of transcript of interview with J.S. by Geldzahler On Edie Sedgewick and Warhol crowd. Only a few paragraphs used in her book. A great record of the Factory 1962-1979, 1973 January (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Jules and Doris Stein: approximately 30 page file. 10 color 8x10 photos of Stein home; 2 page xerox tribute from Stein Institute and Newsletter regarding Jules Stein, 1896-1981; the remainder of file - original drafts and notes, typed and hand correspondence regarding Steins. For an Architectural Digest article on the home of noted Hollywood producer (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Steuben: approximately 30 file and 6 catalogues or booklets (Box 9, Folder 329)
    1) 2 xerox copies of 12 page typed hand corr. ink, draft of essay regarding Stueben glass; 2 page agreement with Geldzahler regarding Services and exhibition; 2) Glass Sculpture by David Dowler: Steuben Glass, published 1980; New Sculpture by Peter Aldridge: Steuben Glass, published 1981; 50 Years on 5th: A Retrospective Exhibition of Steuben Glass, published 1984; The Art of Steuben: Volume IV, published 1987; Sailing by Peter Aldridge from Steuben Glass, - 2 page manuscript date; About Steuben - no published date. Plus a 12 page typescript of history and aesthetic of glassmaking, by Geldzahler, plus another copy corrected in red and green ink by Geldzahler.
  - Steuben Glass: 5 page file - correspondence regarding payment for catalogue introduction (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - diSuvero: 7 page file and catalogue - xerox of press releases and clipping regarding Socrates Sculpture Perk, Athena Foundation 1977-1986 catalogue (Box 9, Folder 331)
  - Tamasaburo: approximately 50 page file - all xerox and original typed draft transcripts of interview (Geldzahler and Tamasaburo Bando). 10 page typescript, heavy editing by Geldzahler; xerox of above, some copy editing; 14 page unedited typescript of above plus one bill, and one letter to Geldzahler from Japan Society, NY, 1984 May (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - Cy Twombly: 2 page xerox from volume 8 of the Journal for Charles Olson studies, essay by Olson on Twombly, used as text to "Poems of the Sea" exhibit at DIA Bridgehampton; book regarding Twombly (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - The Strand: approximately 150 page file - all business papers, leases, shareholder's agreements etc. for South Beach Restaurant Corp. Geldzahler was an investor in this business (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Dorthea Tanning: approximately 175 page file. 11 page typed interview; 1 page typescript letter signed from DT 1/14/87; 12 pages, xerox typescript with corrections for article on DT for Elle magazine; typed version of above; another version with corrections; approximately 35 pages of unedited transcript between Geldzahler and DT; 8 page autograph notes by Geldzahler on DT; 50 pages xeroxed by Geldzahler from DT's autobiography "Birthday.", 1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation: 5 page file - 2 letters from Foundation's requesting Geldzahler to nominate artists, 1 page handwritten, ink, notes by Geldzahler (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - 1986 Venice Biennale Proposal: approximately 100 page file - one press kit; the majority of file is various business correspondence regarding Noguchi exhibition, budget proposals etc.; typed xerox statement by Noguchi, 5 page typed, hand corrected (pencil and pen) of preface Geldzahler on Noguchi. Plus several xeroxed versions of this essay with Geldzahler emendations (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - 41st Venice Biennale 1984: approximately 20 page file incl. xerox blueprint of pavilion; xerox hand corrected (ink) proposal by Geldzahler; (page handwritten, ink) notes by Raymond Foye; various business correspondence and contract (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - 1 8x10 B&W photo of Nancy Grave's Sculpture Five Fans, Lampshades and Lotus, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - 1 8X10 B&W photo of Susan Rothenberg's Untitled painting, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - 1 8x10 B&W photo of Raoul Hague's sculpture Chautauqua, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - 1 8x10 B&W photo of Jess'(?) Fig. 1-A Year's Darling of a Pig My Size, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - 1 8x10 B&W photo of painting (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - 2 page file - letter, typed, hand signed by Musa Mayer to Geldzahler regarding information about father's (Philip Guston) painting and an accompanying form (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - About Geldzahler: approximately 20 page file and catalogues - all clippings (xerox and original) mostly about Geldzahler as Comm. of Cultural Affairs and 4 copies of New Glass Review #3 from the Corning Museum of Glass, 1982, undated (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - About Geldzahler: approximately 5 page file of original clippings (Geldzahler as Commissioner of Cultural Affairs) and 1 copy New York magazine, October 13, 1969 - Geldzahler on page 44. Review of NYPS show. Various NY Times editorials by Geldzahler and stories on Geldzahler. Cue magazine, "The King of NY Culture"; The Wharton Business School magazine, Spring 1981: "Managing the Arts," an interview with Geldzahler; London Times, 7/4/81., 1969-1981 (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1989 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    1) 1 color Polaroid of boy in handcuffs and blindfolded, by Mapplethorpe; 2) Typed postcard from Lannan Foundation regarding check; 3) 2 page letter poem to Geldzahler, ink, from Greg Millard (in envelope); 4) Typed letter to Geldzahler from Mark Lancaster, hand signed (ink); 5) 1 page handwritten (ink) letter to Geldzahler from Louis Lieberman, 3/24/83; 6) 3x5 B&W photo of John McKendry by Dorothy Beskind; 7) 1 page typed, hand signed (ink) letter from James A. Michener to Geldzahler with enclosure, 3/2/65; 8) In envelope - paper cutouts from Moskowitz to Geldzahler for X-mas; 9) Handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Helen Frankenthaler Motherwell with 3 B&W photos in envelope, August 26, 1964; 10) Postcard of Athens to Geldzahler, handwritten, ink, from Helen Frankenthaler Motherwell - no date; 11) Postcard of Cape Cod from H.F.M. to Geldzahler, handwritten, ink, July 28, 1964; 12) Handwritten card, ink, from Tamar Gendler to Geldzahler, November 1986; 13) Program for Gregory Blankinship Millard Memorial, October 1984 - 2 page typed original, hand corr. (ink) testimonial by Geldzahler - 3 xerox copies of same; 14) 4 page section of East Hampton Star, September 11, 1986 - article on Aladar Marberger; 15) 1 page letter, typed, hand signed (ink) to Geldzahler from Edward Meneely and 5 page typed resume; 16) 1 page handwritten letter to Geldzahler, ink, from Teddy Millington-Drake - January 7, 1983; 17) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Teddy Millington-Drake - February 14, 1984; 18) Western Union Mailgram - Confirmation of message from Geldzahler to Teddy Millington-Drake - ½7/84; 19) Postcard to Geldzahler - handwritten, ink, from Jane Meyerhoff - August 29 - no year; 20) 1 page typed hand signed (ink) letter to Geldzahler from Neil Noland, May 7, 1985 - in envelope; 21) 2 page xerox program of "Happening" Sat, May 22, 1965 - Oldenberg event - Geldzahler in program; 22) 1 page xerox of typed, hand signed letter to Geldzahler from Albert Goldman regarding Lennon book; 23) 4 page typed (last page, handwritten, pencil) handsigned (pencil) to Geldzahler from Claes Oldenberg - no date; 24) hand painted postcard to Geldzahler from Shinro Ohtaki, 1984; 25) 3 page handwritten, ink, with color pencil drawing on last page from Shinro Ohtaki to Geldzahler, February 15, 1989; 26) Postcard to Geldzahler, ink, from Thomas Lanigan-Schmidt - no date; 27) Card to Geldzahler, ink, November 2, 1988 from Amy O'Connor; 28) Card - handwritten, green felt pen on blue card from Jackie Onassis to Geldzahler - no date - in envelope; 29) 1 page handwritten letter blue felt pen, to Geldzahler from Jackie Onassis, December 1, 1981 - envelope.
  - Correspondence, 1964-1986 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    1) Postcard of William Hogarth etching to Geldzahler from Philipe Pettit (high wire artist), February 28, 1985; 2) 1 page typed letter, hand signed, ink, to Geldzahler from Trudy C. Kramer - September 12, 1984; 3) "Jacob" postcard to Geldzahler from Daniel Pagano, ink, 2/29/88 - in envelope; 4) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Michael Rauch - December 17, 1985 in envelope; 5) Postcard, October 1965, from Leningrad by James Rosenquist to Geldzahler, ink; 6) 2 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Barbara Rose - circa 1964, news of summer vacation in Mass. with Frank Stella 7) 2 page handwritten letter, ink, from Clement Rosenthal to Geldzahler, December 25 - no year.(Painter, son of French conductor Manuel Rosenthal) 8) 1 page typed, hand signed (ink) letter to Geldzahler from Clement Rosenthal - May 4, 1986, in envelope; 9) Hudson River Piers postcard from Ed Ruscha, ink, to Geldzahler, 1965; 10) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Anne Rorimer, April 28, 1965 - in envelope; 11) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Lady Rupert Neville, May 7, 1983; 12) 1 page handwritten letter, ink, to Geldzahler from Lady Rupert Neville, June 14, 1983; 13) Western Union Mailgram confirmation from Geldzahler to Lady Neville, 5/24/83; 14) 1 page typed, hand signed (ink) letter to Geldzahler from Budd Schulberg - no date; 15) 1 page handwritten letter, ink, notebook paper to Holly and Horace from Tom Schmidt, September 23, 1973 and ripped corner of notebook paper note, ink, to Geldzahler from T.S. - envelope; 16) Poster and accompanying 5 page xerox "The Art of Edward Avedisian and Richard Henessy" by Christopher Scott for exhibition - Grey Art Gallery, February-March 1977; 17) 1 page typed note, hand signed with P.S. (ink) from Jean Stein to Geldzahler - February 3, 1983; 18) Card from florist with handwritten, ink, note to Geldzahler from Beverly Sills - no date; 19) Frank Stella exhibition announcement card. Kasmin Gallery, London 1964 20) One color transparency in envelope from Jack Riggio; 21) 2 page xerox inventory of Christopher Scott, pieces held by Department of Cult. Affairs; 22) 1 page letter to Geldzahler from Stephen Shore, handwritten, ink, 5/5/83; 23) Bright orange card to Geldzahler from Stephen Sprouse, handwritten, ink, and 4 Polaroids of artwork; 24) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from poet, Stephen Spender, May 4, 1983 - in envelope; 25) Helmut Middendorf postcard to Geldzahler from Tomi Skeiff, ink, 1/1/83; 26) Fungus Rock and Qawra Tower postcard to Geldzahler from Tomi Skeiff, ink, January 28, 1984; 27) Card - handwritten, ink, from Jean Stein to Geldzahler - no date 28) Great Goosenecks of the San Juan postcard to Geldzahler from Joel Sokolov, ink, 8/20/84; 29) Xerox of photo - on back - note to Geldzahler from Joel Sokolov, ink, no date; 30) Roma postcard to Geldzahler from Tommy Lanigan Schmidt, ink, 6/15/84; 31) Russian postcard to Larry Stanton from Geldzahler, no date, ink; 32) 1 page handwritten letter, ink, from Geldzahler to Larry Stanton, July 19, 1970 - in envelope; 33) Tunisic postcard to Larry Stanton from Geldzahler, ink, no date; 34) 1 page xerox of NY Native article (November 1984) on Larry Stanton by Dennis Cooper; 35) "Shape and Structure" exhibition announcement card, Tibor de Nagy Gallery, org. by Geldzahler and Frank Stella.
  - Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    1) Isamu Noguchi: October 27-November 8 1986 exhibition announcement card; 2) 1 page typed, hand signed, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Akira Ueda, September 25, 1986; 3) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Bismarck Victoria with exhibition announcement, 1/18/83; 4) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Berkeley Vincent, 12/31/82; 5) 1 page typed letter, hand signed (green felt pen) to Geldzahler from Diana Vreeland, June 2, 1987; 6) 1 page typed letter, hand signed (brown felt pen) to Geldzahler from Diana Vreeland, February 24, 1981; 7) En Parcourant nos campagnes postcard to Geldzahler from Harriet Vincent, October 19, 1988, ink; 8) 1 page xerox "Harry Choice: America Dada" - inside: scrawled picture of butterfly from Andy Warhol - ink, on paper with various notes; printed Christmas card from the Factory - handsigned by Andy and Philipage 9) 2 page handwritten letter, incl. to Geldzahler from Jack Woody - August 1, 1982.(Publisher, Twelvetrees Press) 10) 4 page handwritten, pencil, letter to Geldzahler from Ron Warren - October 6, 1986 - in envelope; 11) 1 page typed letter, hand signed, ink, to Geldzahler from William S. Wilson - no date; 12) Greece postcard to Geldzahler from Jack Whitten, 8/27/84 ink; 13) Greece postcard to Geldzahler from Jack Whitten, 9/5/83 ink; 14) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Jeffrey Wasserman, April 16, 1985 - with enclosed 2 transparencies and xerox of press clippings - in envelope; 15) 1 page typed - hand correspondence and hand signed (ink) letter to Geldzahler from Jonathan Weinberg, April 5, 1984; 16) 2 printed booklets Report to the White House, October 1987, Pres. Task Force on Artist Humanities; invitation to White House and various business related typed correspondence 17) 1 page handwritten letter, ink, May 2, 1988 to Geldzahler from Jack Whitten - in envelope; 18) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Jack Whitten, September 18, 1986.
  - Correspondence, 1963-1987 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    1) 1 page handwritten (ink) letter to Geldzahler from Dan Flavin, May 12, 1965. A statement regarding his work. 2) 1 page typed letter, hand signed (ink) to Geldzahler from Michael Freid - 5/31/63; 3) 3 page letter, handwritten (ink) to Geldzahler from Michael Hurson, 2/21/65; 4) 1 page letter to Geldzahler from Michael Hurson, handwritten (ink), October 15 - no year; 5) 7 page handwritten (ink) letters to Geldzahler from Michael Hurson, 1964-1965 (folded together); 6) 3/1 page letters to Geldzahler from Michael Hurson, July 28, 1965; June 9, 1965; April 2, 1965, handwritten, ink; 7) 1 page handwritten on legal paper (brown felt pen) letter with drawing to Geldzahler from David Hockney - no date - in envelope. This was Steven Mazoh's pool in Rhinebeck, NY, Hockney's first actual painted pool. 8) 13 color snapshots of David Hockney painting bottom of pool/Geldzahler wandering around in pool - in envelope; 9) 9 page handwritten letter (brown ink) to Geldzahler from David Hockney, February 21, 1983 - in envelope and 9 page xerox copy of same. An extensive account of his "new ideas on perception." 10) Marlon Brando postcard to Geldzahler from Mark Gero, November 13, 1987 - ink; 11) 6 page legal paper - handwritten - brown ink - letter to Geldzahler from David Hockney - November 2, 1982 - in envelope. Very personal; 12) Color transparency - Hockney painting of Geldzahler; 13) Taped cardboard packet containing Hockney slides; 14) Wedding printed announcement from Hans Hofmann to Geldzahler, December 8, 1965; 15) 1 page handwritten, ink, letter to Geldzahler from Hans Hofmann - March 15, 1965 - in envelope. On his wife's stationary; 16) 1 page handwritten - ink - letter to Geldzahler from Maude Huffman, September 5, 1983 - in envelope; 17) 1 page typed letter, hand signed, ink, to Geldzahler from Michael Hurson - April 18, 1984; 18) 1 page typed letter, hand signed, ink, to Geldzahler from Michael Hurson, September 17, 1984; 19) 1 page typed letter, hand signed, ink, to Geldzahler from Michael Hurson, September 19, 1986.
  - Correspondence, 1965-1986, undated (Box 9, Folder 351)